{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_1_5GIQVN",
                "player_5_5GIQVN",
                "player_10_5GIQVN",
                "player_4_5GIQVN"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                1,
                5,
                10,
                4
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "stand"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -3026.151,
                    78.685,
                    98.226,
                    0,
                    -94.98698185622541,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -3140.493,
                    287.387,
                    98.226,
                    0,
                    28.791489003797835,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -3026.917,
                    -145.711,
                    98.15,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -2691.406,
                    138.644,
                    98.226,
                    0,
                    64.80962566079802,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -3176.471,
            -6.877,
            98.165
        ],
        "sample_radius": 706.4231623721412
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -3164.339,
            -503.678,
            107.428,
            0,
            71.97551605111504,
            0
        ],
        [
            -2218.964,
            164.793,
            98.21,
            0,
            -174.30343516038457,
            0
        ],
        [
            -3435.806,
            350.531,
            98.15,
            0,
            -29.307357818189125,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the man in light pants and sunglasses, the woman in camo vest or the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. The woman in camo vest",
                    "B. The woman in floral shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. The woman in camo vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the woman in camo vest, the man in light pants and sunglasses or the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses",
                    "B. The man in burgundy polo and light pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the woman in camo vest, the man in light pants and sunglasses or the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses",
                    "B. The woman in floral shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the man in burgundy polo and light pants, the man in light pants and sunglasses or the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses",
                    "B. The woman in camo vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the man in burgundy polo and light pants, the man in light pants and sunglasses or the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses",
                    "B. The woman in floral shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the woman in floral shirt, the man in light pants and sunglasses or the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses",
                    "B. The woman in camo vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. The man in light pants and sunglasses"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a crouch position in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many humans in the scene are lying down?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are in a standing state?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are holding an object?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many male individuals are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many female individuals are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many humans in the scene have a light skin color?",
                "answer": "three"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing sunglasses and a dark green shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "C. liedown"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the green tactical uniform?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the burgundy polo shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. holding something",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "B. holding something"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman wearing the white and blue floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. sit",
                    "C. walk",
                    "D. stand"
                ],
                "answer": "D. stand"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the man in burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            }
        }
    }
}